export const quiz = [
  {
    slug: "shellys-apartment",
    question:
      "What is the name of the apartment building where the main characters live in The Big Bang Theory?",
    answer: "The Pasadena Cheesecake Factory Apartments",
    bookmark: true,
  },
  {
    slug: "shellys-job",
    question:
      "Which character has a Ph.D. in astrophysics and often uses the catchphrase 'Bazinga!'?",
    answer: "Sheldon Cooper",
    bookmark: false,
  },
  {
    slug: "howwys-wife",
    question: "What is the name of Howard Wolowitz's aerospace engineer wife?",
    answer: "Bernadette Rostenkowski",
    bookmark: true,
  },
  {
    slug: "rajesh-dog",
    question:
      "What is the name of Rajesh Koothrappali's beloved Yorkshire Terrier?",
    answer: "Cinnamon",
    bookmark: false,
  },
  {
    slug: "wolly-fan",
    question:
      "Who is known for his love of comic books, action figures, and a specific superhero-themed T-shirt?",
    answer: "Howard Wolowitz",
    bookmark: true,
  },
  {
    slug: "where-are-they-wage-slavin",
    question:
      "What is the name of the university where the main characters work and study?",
    answer: "Caltech (California Institute of Technology)",
    bookmark: false,
  },
  {
    slug: "amy-job",
    question:
      "Which character is a neurobiologist and is often the voice of reason in the group?",
    answer: "Amy Farrah Fowler",
    bookmark: true,
  },
  {
    slug: "penny-wageslave-where",
    question:
      "What is the name of the waitress and aspiring actress whom Leonard falls in love with at first sight?",
    answer: "Penny",
    bookmark: false,
  },
  {
    slug: "shellys-spot",
    question:
      "What is Sheldon Cooper's favorite spot on the couch, where he insists on sitting?",
    answer: "His 'spot'",
    bookmark: true,
  },
  {
    slug: "theme-song",
    question:
      "What is the title of the theme song that plays at the beginning of each episode?",
    answer: '"The History of Everything" by Barenaked Ladies',
    bookmark: false,
  },
];
